To extend the learning rule for a linear neuron to a learning rule we can use for
要将线性神经元的学习规则扩展到
multilayer nets of nonlinear neurons, we need two steps.
多层非线性神经网络，需要两个步骤。
First, we need to extend the learning rule to a single nonlinear neuron.
首先，我们需要将学习规则扩展到非线性神经元。
And we're going to use logistic neurons, although many other kinds of nonlinear
虽然也可以使用其他非线性神经元， 这里我们使用逻辑斯蒂神经元为例。
neurons could be used instead. We're now going to generalize the learning
现在我们要学习规则进行通用化，
rule for a linear neuron to a logistic neuron, which is a non linear neuron.
从线性神经元扩展到非线性的逻辑斯蒂神经元。
So, a logistic neuron, computes its logic, z, which is its total input, its, its bias
逻辑斯蒂神经元，
plus the sum over all its input lines of the value of, on an input line xi times
使用bias 加上所有的输入xi乘以权重wi的加和， 得到其逻辑，z。
the weight on that line, wi. It then gives an output y that's a smooth
然后逻辑函数给出y，其是一个光滑的非线性函数。
nonlinear function of that logit. As shown in the graph here, that function
如图所示，
is approximately zero when z is big and negative, approximately one when z is big
当是z很大的负数的时候，输出近似于0；
and positive, and in bet, in between, it changes smoothly and nonlinearly.
z是很大的正数的时候，输出近似1。 两者之间的时候，其输出是非线性但是是光滑的。
The fact that it changes continuously gives it nice derivatives, which make
其变化的连续性使得求有着良好的导数，
learning easy. So to get the derivatives of a logistic
让学习容易。 要得到逻辑斯蒂神经元
neuron with respect to the weight, which is what we need for learning, we first
相当于权重的导数， 首先要得到逻辑，z
need to compute the derivative of the logit itself, that is the total input with
自己的导数，这个很简单。
respect to our weight, that's very simple. The logit is just a bias plus the sum of
其仅仅是bias 加上
all the input lines of the failure on the input lines times the weight.
所有的输入xi乘以权重wi的加和。
So, when we differentiate with respect to wi, we just get xi.
所以对wi求导，我们得到xi。
So, the derivative of the logit with respect to wi is xi, and similarly, the
所以，z对wi求导得到xi，同样的
derivative of the logit with respect to xi is wi.
对xi求导得到wi。
The derivative of the output with respect to the logic is also simple if you express
如果输出以z的形式来表达，
it terms of the output. So, the output is one / one + e^-z. And dy
其对z求导也很简单。 输出是一除以一加上e的负z次方。
by dz is just y into one - y. That's not obvious.
dy对dz等于y乘以1减去y。这里省略了推导过程。
For those of you who like to see the math, I've put it on the next slide.
如果对推导感兴趣， 我在下一张幻灯片里面列出了详细过程。
The math is tedious but perfectly straightforward so you can go through it
过程比较繁琐，但是非常直观， 你可以自己推导一遍。
by yourself. Now, we've got the derivative, the output
现在你得到相应的相应的导数，
with respect to the logic and the derivative, the logit with respect to the
输出对z的导数，z对权重的导数
weight, we can start to figure out the derivative, the output with respect to the
我们就能得到输出相对于权重的导数了。
weight. We just use the chain rule again.
我们可以使用链式法则。
So, dy by dw is dz by dw times dy by dz. And dz by dw, as we just saw, is xi, dy by
dy对dw的等于dz对dw乘以dy对dz。 dz对dw，我们刚刚提过，其实就是xi
dz is y into one minus y. And so, we now have the learning row for a
dy对dz，等于y乘以1减去y。 现在我们有了逻辑斯蒂神经元的学习规则。
logistic neuron. We've got dy by dw, and all we need to do
我们有了dy对dw，然后需要再使用一次链式法则，
is use the chain rule once more, and multiply it by de by dy.
将其乘以de对dy。
And we get something that looks very like the delta rule.
然后你得到一个很类似于德尔塔法则的式子。
So, the way the arrow changes is we change the weight, de by dwi, is just the sum of
所以我们改变权重的方向，de对dwi，等于
all the row of training cases and of the value on input line xin times the
等于输入xi乘以残差，
residual, the difference between the target and the output, on the actual
即目标值和逻辑斯蒂神经元输出值的差，
output of the neuron. But it's got this extra term in it, which
但是这里还有格外的项，
comes from the slope of the logistic function, which is yn into one - yn.
即逻辑斯蒂函数的斜率，等于yn乘以1减去yn。
So, a slight modification of the delta rule gives us the gradiant decent learning
所以，训练一个逻辑斯蒂单元的梯度下降算法
rule for training a logistic unit.
是一个轻微修改过的德尔塔规则。